Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Previously on "Suits"...
Donna told me there's no one
better
to get rid of Faye
than us.
What did you have in mind?
Why don't we skip the
introductions
and jump right to the suing.
Defend me and win.
and I'll go.
But you cheat. I'll tell
the Bar this firm
should be dismantled
permanently.
- Is this some kind of joke?
- No. it's not.
Harvey Specter and Louis Litt
for the defense. Your Honor.
There is no way they would
have known about
that previous lawsuit if
you hadn't fed it to them.
We didn't feed them anything!
- It was me.
- You don't do something like
that without running it by me.
Don't you talk to me
like that.
I am a senior partner in this...
I'm going against two
of my closest friends.
and I can't even talk
to the one guy
who could understand what
the hell I'm going through.
so I don't give a shit if
you're a senior partner
- or not.
- We had a plan.
Something changed.
I wanna know what it is.
- We can't talk about it.
- God damn it. Harvey.
When in the hell did you stop
trusting me?
They didn't give Mike
that testimony; I did.
I respect you owning up
to your mistake.
but I want you packed
within the hour.
- What?
- You're fired.
What is it now. Faye?
You want me
to shoot my brother?
I'm calling to tell you
Katrina came to me.
and said that she was the one
who gave them
that information. not you.
What did you do?
It doesn't matter
what I did.
What matters is that I was
justified in firing Samantha.
You prove that tomorrow.
I'll honor
our original agreement.
and you won't have to prove
that Samantha fabricated
that evidence.
And if I can't?
Then I'll be forced to put
the only other person who knows
what she did on the stand.
Hey.
- You didn't have to wait up.
- No. I didn't.
But I thought after
a night out with Mike.
I might actually see you smile.
but you're not smiling.
- No. I'm not.
- What happened?
I told Mike I'm calling him
to the stand tomorrow.
What?
Harvey. you can't
do that to them.
Donna. if we don't win
this thing tomorrow.
Faye's putting me
on the stand.
Well. then find another way
that doesn't involve this.
This is the way.
and I came around
because I get that.
Now if you can't get it. too.
I'm not going to debate you
on this.
I'm going to sleep.
Harvey. look.
if you say it's the only way
I believe you.
It's just tonight was supposed
to give you a break.
Not make things worse.
Donna. listen to me.
I know you called Mike
because you knew I needed him.
And for a couple of hours.
I wasn't thinking about
the case or tomorrow
or even how much I miss my mom.
You gave me what I needed.
but it's time for me
to win this thing.
You know...
I never told you
how many times I thought
about us being together
over the years.
It was usually nights
like tonight.
when I didn't know if things
were gonna turn out okay.
but I knew it doesn't matter
if it's Faye or Tanner
or Hardman or Goliath.
whoever it is...
no one stands a chance
against Harvey Specter.
And that's the sexiest thing
in the world.
What are you saying?
I'm saying that
we should go in there
and earn you the best night's
sleep you ever had.
Your Honor. the defense calls
Mike Ross to the stand.
Objection.
my client has a right
to attorney-client privilege.
And per Kern v. California.
I'm not going to ask
about things
since you've been her lawyer.
I'm going to ask about
what happened before.
Then there's nothing for me
to testify to
and Kern doesn't apply.
Are you kidding me?
You went against her
on the very case
you say led to her dismissal.
Is this true. Mr. Ross?
- Yes. Your Honor.
- Then swear him in.
Mr. Ross. isn't it true
that Ms. Wheeler
wiped the floor with you
on the Brick Street
Athletics case?
She won. yes.
And what were your feelings
after she wiped the floor
with you?
Objection. Your Honor.
Baiting.
I'll rephrase.
What were your feelings
after your client lost
his precious little company
that you were trying
to help him start?
- I was upset.
- Upset?
Isn't it true that the night
you lost that case.
you accused me
of fabricating evidence?
- I did. but I...
- And when I denied it.
- what did you say exactly?
- Objection.
The witness can't be asked
to recall the exact words
of conversation
that happened weeks ago.
He can if he has
a perfect memory.
You do have a perfect memory.
don't you. Mr. Ross?
Isn't that what
you're always bragging about?
- Yes. but...
- No buts.
You said she fabricated
evidence.
You said she bribed somebody.
You said she cheated
your client out of his company.
Now. I may not have
a perfect memory.
but I sure as hell
remember that.
- Am I wrong?
- I don't care what I said.
I had no proof that anyone
fabricated anything.
and neither did your client
the night she fired mine.
Oh. she just knew it
in her gut.
Exactly like you did the night
you came screaming at me.
No further questions.
Your Honor.
I said something else
that night
that you've clearly forgotten.
Objection.
We didn't ask...
I said that
you've lost yourself.
and as far as I'm concerned.
that's still true.
And as far as the law
is concerned.
my opening statement
is still true
because it doesn't matter
if Ms. Wheeler
crossed a line or not.
Faye Richardson had cause.
and nothing you say
is gonna change that.
Alex.
what are you doing here?
I guess you've been living
under a rock
because I'm here
to tell you we won.
Faye's gonna be gone.
which means you can come back
and so can Samantha.
That's great.
Katrina.
why do you sound like
I just told you
you have cancer?
I'll tell you why.
because Harvey treated me
like shit.
I got fired.
and then to top it all off.
I haven't heard from a single
one of you until this second.
I get it.
And none of that
would've happened
if we would told you
the truth.
But that was a mistake.
and if no one else
has said it yet.
I'm sorry.
Well. that makes one of you.
Alex. and I appreciate it.
But right now. I'm not
even sure I want to come back.
Thank you.
What the... was that?
It was us
doing what we had to.
Yeah. and that bullshit
might work on everyone else.
but it doesn't work on me.
- Robert...
- God damn it. Louis!
You were supposed to be
on her side.
Listen to me.
I know how this looks.
but you are gonna have
to trust us.
Well. that's getting pretty
hard to do.
And after that little stunt
with Mike.
Samantha's only move
is to drop this thing
unless you can tell me...
What?
No. she can't do that.
Well. Louis. it sounds
like you give a shit
about what we do after all.
So fix this goddamn thing
or I'm gonna fix it myself.
Good. you're here.
So are you. but not for long
because I did what you asked.
And if you think you're
gonna weasel out of this...
I'm not weaseling
out of anything.
But you haven't done
what I asked. at least not yet.
- What are you talking about?
- Tomorrow morning.
you're taking the stand
against Samantha.
What did you just say?
I said you're taking
the stand.
- Bullshit. I am!
- Harvey...
No. you said we didn't have
to prove she did anything.
And I also said
we needed to win.
We did win.
No. it looks like
we're going to win.
But this is my integrity
on the line.
and I'm not leaving things
to chance.
And if you try to walk away.
I'll subpoena you.
put you up as
a hostile witness.
and cross you myself.
You know what. I am hostile.
but you're every bit
as vindictive
as I said you are.
And you pretend
to be Robin Hood
when you're really just
a snake oil salesman.
Well. I'm not buying it.
So one way or another. you're
taking the stand tomorrow.
and you're telling the truth.
What are you doing here?
I'm here because it's time
I told you the truth.
Is this. uh. something
we're gonna need whiskey for?
Faye offered a deal.
Win and she leaves.
Refuse to help. and she goes
after Samantha's license.
Then to hell with this case.
I'll call Samantha. We'll
drop this thing right now.
That's not an option.
Never was.
Because if Faye suspects us
of tanking it...
She won't just stay here.
She'll wipe us off the map.
And the cherry on top.
she's putting me
on the stand tomorrow.
What?
Harvey. Samantha told you
the truth.
You can't take the stand.
I've been over it
from every angle.
We can't stop it.
There's only one thing
left for me to do.
Wait. please tell me that
you are not planning on lying.
Mike. it's the only way.
I say I can't remember.
Faye'll call me before the Bar.
I'll just stick
to my story.
And then she will convince
them to take your license.
and what the hell
did we do this for?
You did it for me.
That's the end of it.
I just came here to tell you
that I never stopped
trusting you.
No.
We're not going down this way.
Did you hear me?
I just told you I already
looked at every possibility.
And what was the first thing
you taught me to do
when someone puts a gun
to your head?
There aren't 146 ways
out of this.
Good.
'cause all we need is one.
And the answer to this
is to take that gun back.
and point it at
her goddamn head.
And I'm telling you Faye
isn't like anyone else.
We can't just blackmail her.
She won't fold.
Well. then we have
to make her think that
if she hands us in. they're
gonna believe us. not her.
Meaning?
Harvey. you and I conned
the world for years.
I think it's time
for one last con.
All right. Robert.
we have our drinks.
I'm here.
Now. what is it?
You know what it is.
You saw what happened today.
And if you're about
to suggest I drop this thing...
I'm about to tell you
I saw Louis.
and they're not gonna
back down.
Then bring on tomorrow.
because all they have
is hearsay.
And that doesn't mean
you won't lose.
Samantha. you don't have
any more cards to play.
And Mike said the exact
same thing an hour after court.
Then listen to him.
because that boy
has never waved the white flag
in his life.
Oh. yes. he has.
He was a fraud who went
on trial knowing he was guilty.
but he still fought
tooth and nail
until he lost faith
in himself.
The second he did that.
that's when he went to prison.
Well. this is not
the same as that.
You're right because
they had him dead to rights.
but they don't have us.
Oh. they've got us.
all right.
and it's a lot worse than
you think.
What are you talking about?
Harvey cut a deal with Faye.
They beat us fair and square.
she tells the Bar they don't
need oversight anymore.
and she leaves you alone.
But now she's coming
after your license anyway.
Then all that's left for us
to do is win.
That's not gonna happen.
She subpoenaed Harvey
to testify tomorrow.
When why the hell
did you just waltz in here
like it's a Sunday afternoon?
Because what you're saying is
win or lose. we're screwed.
No. we're not. Samantha.
She is.
'Cause Harvey
taught me what to do
when your back's up
against the wall.
You break
the goddamn thing down.
And I'm guessing you have
the keys to the bulldozer?
Yes. I do.
They called Harvey.
I think it's time we called
a witness of our own.
You've got to be kidding me.
Harvey sends you here
to get me to save him
when he hasn't
even apologized to me.
Katrina. he sent me here
because he felt like shit
about how he treated you.
He wanted to come himself.
and I insisted it be me.
Why?
Because you knew
he wasn't really sorry?
Because this isn't just
to help him.
It's to help all of us.
And it's one thing for me
to bluff
that I'm going to lie
on the stand.
You're asking me to
out and out participate
in an extortion scheme.
No. I'm not.
No one has to know
you were in on it.
She'll know and I'll know.
and I'm not doing it.
- Katrina...
- Enough bullshit. Alex.
I'd still have a job if Harvey
had shown me the respect
to tell me about that deal.
So if you can't be straight
with me about this.
you can get the hell out.
All right.
No bullshit.
It's extortion.
And if you don't want to.
we can try to find another way.
But Faye is the one
who fired you. not Harvey.
You know in your heart
he's sorry about what he did.
and all I'm really asking you
is to speak your goddamn mind.
What if it doesn't work?
Then we all go down.
because there is no way Faye
ever believes all of us
weren't a part of it.
What about Mike and Samantha?
Did you run this by them yet?
I have.
They're in.
Well. then I'm in. too.
and I can get us
the last person we need.
Not the last person. Louis.
You heard the plan.
There's one more. and Alex
is making that happen.
But if this thing goes south.
the firm is done.
So I'm putting this
to a formal vote.
I already said I'm in.
As far as I'm concerned. this
should've been done months ago.
- Then it's settled.
- One more thing.
We're all that's left
of Pearson Hardman.
If this turns out
to be the end.
I want you both to know
there's no one I'd rather have
by my side than you.
Gretchen. you alone?
Not anymore.
Louis. what are you doing here?
I'm here because
we have a plan
to get Faye out of our lives
once and for all.
and we need your help.
but it's not just risking
your job this time.
It can constitute perjury
which means...
Louis. I've been working
in law firms
since you were in diapers.
I know what it means.
and whatever it is.
I'm in.
Are you sure?
When I first came
to work on your desk.
I thought to myself.
"I can't spend another second
with this lunatic."
Don't get me wrong.
you're still a lunatic.
but this all goes to shit.
so be it 'cause I know
whose team I'm on.
Then let's get
the hell out of here
so I can take you out
to dinner as colleagues.
Louis. you don't have
to do that.
Yeah. Gretchen. I do.
Because after tomorrow.
we might not be colleagues
anymore.
Alex take care of it?
He did.
Harvey. what's going on?
Nothing. it's just a lot
of people
are putting themselves
on the line for this.
The train is moving. but it
hasn't left the station yet.
I don't understand.
Are you looking for me
to stop you?
It's just I know you've
always been my compass.
And I need to be sure that
you're really on board.
Listen to me.
I know who I'm with.
and I don't wanna change you.
I wanna be with you.
But if this is about
everybody else
and you're still not sure.
then the train doesn't really
leave the station
until tomorrow.
Then there's one more thing.
I have an ace in the hole.
but I don't wanna play it
unless you're good with it too.
Katrina. you're
not permitted to be here.
This won't take long. Faye.
I just wanted
to let you know that
if Harvey testifies tomorrow.
so will I.
Excuse me?
I've been called as a witness
for the plaintiff.
and I plan to tell that jury
exactly why I was fired.
So what?
You were fired for cause.
That's your story.
Mine is that you asked me
to use my friendship
with the other side.
and when I refused.
you got rid of me.
- That's a lie.
- It's also the third time
you'll be accused
of wrongful termination.
Only this time.
it's a crime.
Then go ahead.
Nobody will believe you.
I think they will because
they're going to ask me
if on your second day here.
you approached me
to undercut Samantha.
Then they're going to ask
if you came to Alex Williams
to spy on Samantha.
And the last thing
they're going to ask
is if I'm so untrustworthy.
then why did you
specifically choose me
to write the firm's
code of conduct?
I thought you were better
than the rest of them.
And you think
you're better than everyone.
It's up to you. Faye.
But like I said. if Harvey
testifies then so do I.
You put them up to this.
didn't you?
Put who up to what?
All right.
you wanna play that game.
Katrina Bennett marched
into my office
threatening to make it
look like I crossed a line
to win this case
if I go make you testify.
So don't tell me you didn't
put her up to this.
Sounds to me like she did it
because she can't stand you.
Don't bullshit me. Harvey.
I'm not bullshitting.
I didn't go see Katrina
about anything.
You're parsing your words.
Someone did it
and they did it for you.
Okay. Faye.
you want a direct statement?
I had nothing to do with this.
Then prove it by quashing
this testimony.
You want to run that
by me again?
I called for
a one-day continuance.
and I want her off that witness
list before you take the stand.
All right.
you want me to do this?
Then you're gonna do
something for me.
Like what?
What I should have had you do
the second I entered
into this nightmare.
You're going to put our
entire agreement into writing
because I'm not letting
you move the goalposts
another .........- inch.
I haven't moved anything
anywhere.
Now who's bullshitting. Faye?
Take it or leave it.
Type up the agreement.
I'll sign it tomorrow.
What was that?
Faye's moving faster
than I thought.
What's going on here?
This was supposed
to be between me and you.
No. Faye. this is between
you and the firm.
And Harvey's
not doing anything
without all of us here
to witness it.
So you're going
to sign that agreement.
and you're gonna
pack your bags.
and I never want
to see you again.
I'm not packing anything
until the jury
returns a verdict.
So let's sign this thing
and get it over with
because you have
some testimony to prepare.
Give it to her. Gretchen.
Okay.
everything looks in order.
The hell it does.
Your lawyer tampered with
my goddamn witness.
Bullshit.
I didn't tamper with anyone.
You gonna say you didn't
anonymously send Katrina
the criminal code for perjury
to intimidate her?
God damn it. did you play
dirty in my name?
Because if you did. I...
You won't do shit. Faye.
All I did was stop her from
testifying like you asked.
You asked him
to go to my witness?
Don't you dare try
to twist this.
We're not twisting anything.
And when you call Harvey
to the stand.
I'll ask one question.
Did you tell him to shut down
Katrina Bennett or not?
And then we'll ask
if you convinced Katrina
to perjure herself.
You .........- coward.
She's got you so wrapped
around her finger...
The... did you
just say to me?
Hey. back the hell off
my lawyer.
I'm not backing off anything.
Least of all.
this little piece of shit.
Enough!
You lay another finger on
anyone in my firm
and you'll be up
for assault charges.
And if you two don't get out
of here inside five seconds.
I'm telling the judge you came
in here to get a mistrial.
You heard the woman.
Get the hell out.
You know what?
You people make me sick.
and I can't wait
to put you all behind me.
Well. then don't wait. Faye.
Get the hell out right now.
- Excuse me?
- He said you're done here.
Because that document
you just put your name to?
Gretchen switched it
on your ass during the fight.
And it's now an order
for Harvey to witness tamper
by any means necessary.
I get it.
You think you set me up.
No. Faye.
we did set you up.
Because first you ordered
Katrina to fire Samantha.
and then you ordered me
to witness tamper.
Well. I don't care
what you had me sign.
No one's gonna believe
you didn't trick me.
Well. we think they will
because Katrina came
to see you last night
and there's record of it
in the lobby downstairs.
And after she did.
you went to see Harvey.
and there's a record
of that too.
And when I refused contact
with Katrina.
you called Gretchen
into your office
and had her send
the criminal code
to intimidate her
out of testifying.
This is bullshit.
It may be bullshit.
but to a jury. it's gonna
look like a hot fudge sundae.
Face it.
It's over.
You think you're going
to bully me into something?
I don't care
if it costs me everything.
- I will never back down!
- Damn it. Faye!
I said never!
Then you'll end up
in prison.
And you wouldn't
have done any of this
if it weren't for him.
because he is a blight.
He's a goddamn hero!
Okay. stop.
Everybody. give me
and Faye a minute alone.
- Harvey. what are you...
- It's okay. Louis.
I got it.
What are you gonna do now?
Break my kneecaps?
No. Faye.
I'm going to give you
the thing you wanted
since the day you got here.
but not the way
you wanted it.
What do you think
is going on in there?
It's hard to say.
If I know Harvey.
he's pulling out all the stops.
And that still doesn't mean
he'll be able to convince her.
Louis. have a little faith.
Has Harvey ever
let us down before?
No. not when
it really mattered.
And I'm not about
to start now.
Wait. does that mean...
That Faye's out?
It sure as hell does.
Holy shit.
The firm is ours again.
It is. Louis.
She's packing her shit
as we speak.
Well. then my first order
of business
is bringing you back.
I second that.
If for no other reason
than for finally giving Harvey
what he's always had coming.
Speaking of which.
you're supposed
to pull your punches.
I did.
I can't help if you're
as weak-jawed as Mike.
- Oh. taking shots at me now?
- It's what Harvey would do.
She's right.
I would.
I feel that.
Harvey.
I've got to know.
What did you do
to get Faye to go?
What do you mean
what did I do?
I'm the best closer
this city's ever seen.
I closed.
Seriously. Harvey.
I've got to know.
And I hate to tell you this.
Louis. but you never will.
Harvey. come on.
Okay. you really want
to know?
I gave her Boardwalk
and Park Place.
- Oh. God damn it.
- Harvey. leave him alone.
I want to say something.
Faye's gone because
we all risked everything
for each other.
It's what we've always done.
And we do it for one reason:
we love each other.
And if that doesn't
deserve drinks.
I don't know what does.
Amen to that.
First round's on me.
I owe you all
at least that much.
Come on.
Let's go.
Gretchen?
Tell them to go on without me.
There's something
I need to take care of.
Thanks for meeting with me.
Stan.
I know it's late.
but it's about my wedding.
Ah. I see.
What is it?
I've been wanting
to ask you something
and I've been afraid.
but I'm not anymore.
Stan. I want you
to officiate my wedding.
First of all. Louis.
I am touched.
But?
This is the second time
you've asked me to break
the therapeutic relationship.
If I am to do this.
it won't be like before.
I will no longer
be your therapist.
I knew you were gonna
say that
Then why are you asking me.
Louis?
Because you are not going
to change my mind.
Stan. we were in
the fight of our lives
for the soul of our firm.
And the other night.
Harvey lost it at Katrina.
Katrina. my protégé.
And instead
of losing it back at him
or freaking out
and making it worse.
I calmed him down.
You calmed Harvey down?
Stan. I'm not saying I won't
need therapy again.
- Lord knows I will.
- That's for sure.
I'm saying
I can find someone else
because I'm ready
to have you as a friend.
Then...
It would be my honor
to perform your ceremony.
Thank you.
You know.
when you think about it.
as my friend. you can still
sort of be my therapist.
Louis.
let me be perfectly clear.
When I say friends.
I mean friends as in.
"I need help moving my piano."
Whoa. back the... up. Stan.
We just started being friends
two seconds ago.
Find someone else to move
your goddamn piano.
Are you gonna ask me to
pick you up at LaGuardia too?
Feed your cat?
Wash your back?
Louis. exactly what kind
of friends do you have?
The best kind.
and you're one of them.
See you at the wedding.
- Louis.
- Harvey!
Where have you been?
The only two people
in the wedding party
are you and Sheila's sister.
and I haven't seen either one
of you all day.
Louis. relax.
Everything's under control.
Wait a second.
Are you wearing
a morning coat?
Of course I'm wearing
a morning coat.
Frankly.
I'm disappointed you're not.
You didn't tell me to.
Well. I thought it went
without saying.
This is just a regular tux.
You might as well
be wearing assless chaps!
Louis. you're not
the Prince of England.
No. I'm just someone who
regrets asking a complete slob
to be his best man.
Well. if you really feel that
way. I can step down right now.
Don't be ridiculous.
you look fantastic.
Truth be told. I don't look
nearly as good as you.
- You really mean that?
- Of course not.
You look like Mr. Peanut.
God damn it. Harvey.
I'm about to get married.
The last thing I need is for
you to make me feel less than.
Less than?
Less than what?
It's an expression. asshole.
You're gonna make me feel
shitty about that too?
- You make it happen?
- Mission accomplished.
- What are you talking about?
- Sheila asked me to ask Harvey
to get you to freak out
about something.
What?
Why would she do that?
Because if you're freaking
out on Harvey.
you're not freaking out about
the fact that Sheila's sister
is stuck on the L.I.E..
and I'm gonna fill in.
Wait. so this was just
to get me distracted?
That's what a best man does.
Louis.
Today. I'm here for you.
Whatever you need.
I think I might cry.
Well. you better hold it
together another five minutes
because it's time
we walk down that isle.
Don't get any ideas about us
doing this any time soon.
Now's not
the time. Harvey.
What better time is there?
Sometimes you meet two people
who were so perfectly made
for each other.
it is hard to envision one
without the other.
Each one compliments
the other.
such that they are as
important to each another
as air and water
are to life.
I have known Louis many years.
We have been through
thick. thin.
and everything in between.
I am proud to call him
my friend.
And when I met Sheila.
I knew she was
the perfect fit for him.
Like Cinderella's
glass slipper.
Damn it. Stan. I told you
not to talk about that.
Our sex life isn't up for...
Louis. it is a fairy tale.
No one knows about...
Sorry.
Carry on.
As I was saying...
In this particular case.
I would say there are
no two people on this earth
more made for each other than...
Oh. God.
Sheila. you're
not supposed to say that
until he's going to
ask you to say I do.
- Louis. my water just broke.
- Holy shit.
Louis. stay calm.
Now's not the time to...
I've never been more calm
in my life. Donna.
Stan. ask us if we do.
Louis. do you take Sheila
to be your wife?
I do.
Sheila.
- I do.
- Stan.
I now pronounce you
man and wife.
Harvey. Donna.
give me the rings.
Sheila. let's get you
to that ambulance.
You have an ambulance
waiting?
Of course I do.
She's nine months pregnant.
I didn't want
to leave anything to chance.
Louis. honey. I'm so sorry
I just ruined our wedding.
Ruined it?
Sheila. we just got married
and our baby is on the way.
This is the best day
of my life.
- You really mean that?
- Of course I do!
Our anniversary
and our child's birthday
are gonna be
on the same day.
And look...
our chariot awaits.
Thank you so much. Louis.
I don't know what
I'd do without you.
I love you. Sheila.
Come on.
let's go have the baby.
Oh. my God.
That was so embarrassing.
My water just broke
in our ceremony.
Sheila.
we have been over this.
It's wonderful.
What changed?
What changed is I'm in labor.
and you're just sitting there
doing nothing.
Well. we're in an ambulance.
What the... can I do?
You can stab a fork
in your eye
and show me
we're in this together!
I should have asked Stan
to come on
the ambulance with us.
Are you seriously telling me
that I'm crazy right now?
Is that the intercom?
I think they need me
in the front.
Oh. my God.
This was a huge mistake.
I think I might be
having triplets.
Sheila. hey. hey. hey!
Look at me!
I'm right here.
I swear. 30 minutes tops
we'll be in that delivery room.
- Breathe. breathe. breathe.
- Okay.
That was a bad one.
- Any word?
- What do you mean "word"?
You want me to call Louis
while his wife is in labor?
I rather call anybody else
about anything else.
- Harvey.
- No. Donna. he's right.
It's a stupid question.
It's not a stupid question.
We all just don't know
what to do.
I mean. the only time
I've been to a wedding
that got cut short.
you went to prison.
Nothing?
Come on. that is some
A+ material right there.
- Is this thing on?
- Oh. it's not that.
It's just... look at this.
Nobody's dancing.
Of course
they're not dancing.
It's weird.
It's like they have nothing
to celebrate.
What do you say we give them
something to celebrate?
Wait.
What are you saying?
I'm saying I love you.
And whether I knew it or not.
I wanted to marry you
from the second I met you.
Oh. my God!
Donna Roberta Paulsen.
will you marry me
right here. right now?
Harvey. of course
I'll marry you.
but right now our families
aren't here
- and I don't have a dress and...
- Wait. stop.
You look beautiful.
We can do it again
for our families.
But...
If there's one thing
I learned from my mom.
it's that I wasted
too much time.
First. not forgiving her.
And then not admitting
how I feel about you.
Well. I don't want
to waste another second.
Please. will you
marry me tonight?
What about rings?
We don't have any rings.
You can find one for me.
but I have one for you.
That's what was
in the envelope.
What do you say?
I say yes. Harvey.
Yes.
Everyone. I have
an announcement to make.
As soon as we can write
our vows.
Donna and I
are getting married.
I'd offer to officiate
but I'm not licensed.
and I just don't think
we want to open up
that can of worms again.
Jesus Christ. Louis.
you said a half an hour tops.
It's been 32 minutes!
Damn it. Sheila.
it's just two .........- minutes.
Would you say that
if your face were on fire?
Sheila. listen to me.
This is just one more step
on our road to being a family.
We overcome this.
we overcome anything.
Okay. then you need to get
to overcoming the paperwork
because if I have to have
another contraction
before I get an epidural.
one of us isn't going
to make it. Louis.
- and it isn't going to be me.
- Okay.
Mr. Litt.
Oh. thank God they called
ahead. My wife is in labor.
- We need a room. we need it now.
- I understand that.
Unfortunately. we don't have
any rooms at the moment.
Wait. I'm sorry. What do you
mean you don't have any rooms?
We're having a baby.
It's not going to wait.
Sir. if you'll just calm
down. We will get you a room...
Calm down? I'm supposed
to be on a helicopter
to the Hamptons tonight.
Do you know what the weather's
like in the Hamptons right now?
Neither do I
because I'm not there!
Mr. Litt?
We need to admit your wife
right now.
I know that. That's what I'm
trying to tell everyone.
I mean she needs to get
to the O.R. immediately.
The O.R.?
Is something wrong?
There are some complications.
Your wife and child
are in danger.
Your wife's in
a great deal of pain
and she's in no condition
to make a decision.
We need you to give consent
to her going into surgery
and we need it now.
Go.
I'll sign whatever you need.
Love is a terrifying thing.
It's not safe.
Because when you love someone.
you have to face the fact
that you could lose them.
Sometimes life throws
an unexpected wrench
in your way.
It might be that
you're in jeopardy
of losing your career.
your freedom.
or worst of all.
you might even find out
that a loved one has died.
These things make you realize
how precious life is.
how important every second
we have on this earth is.
and how important the people
we care about are to us.
Donna...
I kept my feelings inside
for so long
because I was afraid.
But when I finally
got good news.
that's when I knew
you were my everything.
I knew I could always count on
you when the chips are down.
I just hadn't realized
I couldn't do without you
when they were up.
I'm a gambler.
I always have been
and I always will be.
When you're with me.
my chips are always up.
None of us know how much
time we really have.
It could be a minute.
It could be an hour.
It could be 50 years.
But I know even
if it's 100 years.
I'll never have enough time
with you.
From the day we are born.
we look for love.
Because it is love
that nourishes our soul.
And when we are lucky enough
to find it.
our lives are changed forever.
- Mr. Litt?
- Please tell me.
I have great news.
Both mother and daughter
are doing fine.
Daughter?
Yes. you have
a beautiful baby girl.
Six pounds.
eight ounces.
Thank you.
You make me laugh.
You make me cry.
You make me crazy.
But most of all. Harvey.
you make me happy.
Without you. I'm empty.
I can never go back
to the way I was before.
You've changed me.
And you've changed my life
forever.
I love you. Harvey Specter.
I love you. Donna Paulsen.
Do you. Harvey Specter.
take Donna Paulsen to be
your lawfully wedded wife?
I do.
Do you. Donna Paulsen.
take Harvey Specter to be
your lawfully wedded husband?
I do.
Then I now pronounce
you man and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
And to add to the good news.
I just heard from Louis.
He's the proud father
of a beautiful baby girl.
Harvey.
I want to go see Louis.
And we will.
But right now.
I want to dance with my wife.
Mr. Litt?
Your wife's still
in recovery.
but would you like
to hold your girl?
Of course.
There you go.
Hi.
Welcome to the world.
I'm Dada.
And I know it was
a bumpy start.
But if one thing is for sure.
I'm always gonna love you.
Do you have a name?
Lucy.
- Our daughter's name is Lucy.
- Are you sure?
Do you wanna wait
to double check with your wife?
No. it's what we both wanted.
I mean. there was a phase
where we thought about Endora.
- but we came to our senses.
- Endora?
We're big fans
of "Bewitched."
- But wasn't she the bad guy?
- She knew who she was.
I've been up all night.
Can we just drop it?
- Hi. Daddy.
- Hi.
Is that her?
Yes.
Can I hold her?
Donna. this is Lucy.
Hi. sweetheart.
Nice to meet you.
Congratulations.
We are gonna have
so much fun together.
Oh. are you hungry?
It's time for me
to take her back.
Oh.
That's okay.
We'll have plenty of time
to get to know her.
We will. Louis.
but not exactly how you think.
Because we have
some news too.
I know.
you guys got married too.
I heard.
Congratulations.
That's not all of it. Louis.
Donna and I talked it over.
and we're leaving the firm.
What?
We're going to Seattle
to work with Mike and Rachel.
No. you can't do that.
- Louis...
- Wait a second. Harvey.
Is this what you did
to close Faye?
Because she's gone now.
She can't stop you from...
It is what
he told Faye. Louis.
But it's what we want.
Both of us.
Bullshit. you've never wanted
to play in the B leagues.
Louis. if there's one thing
that Faye did for me.
it's remind me of who I am.
I like crossing lines.
I like playing in the gray.
But what Mike showed me.
I want to do it
for the good guys for a change.
You said you'd always
be there.
You said you'd never leave.
I meant we'd be there
for as long as you needed us.
You don't need us anymore.
And no matter where we are.
we'll always be your family.
Promise?
We promise.
Well. well. well.
look who's calling.
Guess where I'm sitting
right now.
Back in your old office?
Back in Faye's old office.
Which just happens to be
my old office.
Now that you mention it.
I guess it is.
I always you knew
were out to get me.
It's called
the long con. Robert.
Mm-hmm.
Congratulations. Samantha.
Use it well.
I will. Robert.
I will.
Hey. shouldn't you be
at the hospital?
Sheila's taking a nap.
It's a good thing
you're sitting down
because I have some news.
Is it about Harvey and Donna?
Because I already know.
- It is.
- It's a lot to lose.
I know.
Here's what I also know:
if I were ever backed
into a corner.
there's no one I'd rather have
by my side than you.
What are you saying?
I'm saying I need you
to be my Harvey.
Well. I can't be
your Harvey. Louis.
but I can be your Samantha.
And I'm gonna start with
putting two conditions on it.
Of course you are.
First. we put it
in the bylaws
that we don't change
the name again
for at least five years.
And second?
Before we do that.
we make one final change.
Hey...
what are you doing?
Louis told me he did
this with Jessica
the night before Mike
went to prison.
Looked out on everything
they might be giving up.
This is where it all started
for me and Louis.
Not to mention for Mike.
Are you sure you want
to do this. Harvey?
Are you sure you want to go?
I am.
No turning back now.
Good.
'cause your new boss called.
He'll be here in an hour.
Wants to have a word.
Mike.
what are you doing here?
I didn't think I'd see you
till my first day.
Well. I'll tell you
what I'm doing here.
You may be moving to Seattle.
but...
you don't have a job yet.
I get it.
You want to interview me?
Well. I don't see
another way around it.
Otherwise. how am I gonna know
what I'm getting?
You want to know
what you're getting?
You're getting a guy who
doesn't like
to hang out with people
that aren't that bright.
You know. just to see how
the other half lives.
All right. well.
let me tell you something.
This isn't elementary school.
This is high pressure.
long hours.
I need a grown goddamn man.
Well. I see you've got
a Barbri legal handbook there.
Oh. this old thing?
Go ahead.
Open it.
Any page.
Ask me anything.
You really want
to keep going with this?
No.
I won't know a thing.
Well. did you at least bring
a briefcase full of weed?
No. but I know a guy.
- Coffee cart.
- You got it.
You're hired.
You wanna go see him
for old times' sake?
There'll be plenty of time
for that in Seattle.
Well. I'll see you there.
Harvey.
- Hey.
- Yeah?
You give me this chance.
I promise you I will school
those Harvard douches.
and be the best lawyer
you've ever seen.
Okay. fine. but you've
got to lose the fat tie.
First impressions last.
You get stuck behind
a fat tie.
you're never gonna get out
in front.
Louis. they said
you wanted to see me.
What are you all doing here?
It wasn't just Louis
that wanted to see you.
It was all of us.
And you're here because we
need to ratify the new bylaws.
and we need all
the name partners to do it.
I don't understand.
You're making me
name partner?
What's not to understand?
If it weren't for you.
none of us would be
here right now.
I don't know what to say.
Say yes because
we just put the new name up.
and I already agreed not to
change it again for five years.
I got you
new business cards...
it would be
a really big pain in the ass.
Then yes!
And thank you.
It's an honor.
Good. because it's gonna
take all three of us
to keep this douchebag
in line.
Wait. hold on a second.
It's Sheila calling.
And I want a chance
to respond to that asshole.
Hi. Sweetie.
How are you?
I'm good. Louis.
I just wanted to let you know
that she's sleeping
like the angel she is.
I'll be there as soon
as I can.
We'll both be waiting
for you.
I love you. Sheila.
I love you too.
It's time. Harvey.
You ready to go?
You go ahead without me.
They're packing up
the place tomorrow.
and I need a little more time
before they do.
I understand.
See you at home.
Hey.
You know I couldn't have done
any of this without you.
Any of what?
Everything.
- Whoa.
- You give me this.
and I will become the best
lawyer you have ever seen.
If you start behind
the eight ball.
you'll never get in front.
Some people love
the taste of blood.
Better to find out who you
are sooner than later.
Salieri. Mozart.
Are you wearing braces?
Let me guess.
You're Donna.
Oh. you have no idea
how Donna I am.
Yeah. baby!
Butch and Sundance are back.
Anyone comes at you
with any threat at all.
you come to me.
You tell me!
You tell me everything!
I'm a fraud.
We're not just colleagues
or even friends.
We're family.
To Pearson. Specter. Litt.
Life is like this.
And I like this.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org